onlinepoker.net 2005-12-14

# AustralianMedia.com: Privacy Statement.

**Australian Media Pty Ltd** respects your privacy. Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to **Australian Media Pty Ltd** will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. 

**1\. Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**   
**Australian Media Pty Ltd** does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists. 

**2\. Browser information collected on the website:**   
**Australian Media Pty Ltd** analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on website. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. 

**3\. Advertisements:**  
We have ads served onto our site by Advertising.com. To visit their privacy statement, [**please click here**](http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html). 

**4\. Use of cookies:**   
Australian Media Pty Ltd does not use cookies on this site, or any of its network of sites. 

**5\. Secure Transactions:**   
Australian Media Pty Ltd maintains a secure server for orders at: [**https://www.australianmedia.com**](https://www.australianmedia.com/). 

We use [**Thawte**](http://www.thawte.com/) for our digital certificate. We use a secure server employing 128 bit data encryption to give you the highest level of security in credit card transactions.   

**5\. Currency of Privacy Statement:**  
**Australian Media Pty Ltd** reserves the right to withdraw these "terms of use" and "privacy statement" at any time. We reserve the right to re-issue a replacement "terms of use" and "privacy statement" at any time. We advise that you regularly check: [**http://www.australianmedia.com/termsofuse.htm  
(Terms Of Use)**](http://www.australianmedia.com/termsofuse.htm) and [**http://www.australianmedia.com/privacystatement.htm  
(Privacy Statement)**](http://www.australianmedia.com/privacystatement.htm) regularly.
